Sherin Atapattu

Colombo, Western Province, Sri Lanka



sherinatapattu@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/sherin-atapattu-9b99b5131

Summary

A front-end web developer with more than 6 years of experience in the industry, currently working as a Software Engineer. Expertise in HTML, CSS, SCSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Angular Material, Typescript, Jquery and MySQL. A passion for UI and Frontend development using frameworks (Angular 2+). Unit testing skills with Jasmine & Karma framework. Visit yummyceylon.com for my personal blog.

Experience

Software Engineer

iVedha Inc.

Aug 2022 - Present (9 months)



Engineer - Ul

Virtusa

Nov 2018 - Aug 2022 (3 years 10 months)



Associate Software Engineer

cyclomax International (pvt) Ltd Jan 2017 - Sep 2018 (1 year 9 months)

Education



London Metropolitan University

BSc (Hons) - First Class, Computer Science 2015 - 2018



National Institute of Business Management

2015 - 2017



Royal International School

1996 - 2008

Skills

Jira • Bitbucket • PrimeNG • Clr • Microsoft Office • JavaScript • HTML • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • MySQL • SASS